Killing Kennedy is a drama film directed by Nelson McCormick.
Drama documentary based on Bill O'Reilly's and Martin Dugard's 2012
non-fiction book "Killing Kennedy: The End of Camelot".
It follows the parallel lives of John F.
Kennedy and Lee Harvey Oswald from the winter 1959-1960 to those fatal days in Dallas in November 1963, when
they both died within two days after each other and were buried on the same day - John F.
Kennedy in a state funeral in Washington D.C., broadcast live both to Europe and the Pacific, while Oswald was
buried in Forth Worth at a small funeral where the attending reporters were asked to act as pallbearers.
John F. Kennedy, played by Rob Lowe.
Lee Harvey Oswald, played by Will Rothhaar.
Jacqueline Kennedy, played by Ginnifer Goodwin.
Marina Oswald, played by Michelle Trachtenberg.
Robert F. Kennedy, played by Jack Noseworthy.
Jack Ruby, played by Casey Siemaszko.
Killing Kennedy is a 2013 American docudrama TV film directed by Nelson McCormick and written by Kelly
Masterson, based on the 2012 non-fiction book of the same title by Bill O'Reilly and Martin Dugard.
The film stars Rob Lowe, Will Rothhaar, Ginnifer
Goodwin, and Michelle Trachtenberg.
It dramatizes the presidency and assassination of John F.
Kennedy, as well as the life of Lee Harvey Oswald in the
years leading up to the assassination.
It premiered in the United States and Canada on National Geographic Channel on November 10, 2013,
followed by the various European National Geographic channels a few days later.
It was first shown on terrestrial TV in the UK by Channel 4 on
November 23, 2013 and in South Korea on November 21, 2013.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.